Tufts Weekly UP056
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 22, 1909; UP056.001.005.00057; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.42 Megabytes (Box 5)
    Alumni trustees. All Around Club. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 29, 1909; UP056.001.005.00058; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.74 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 5, 1909; UP056.001.005.00059; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.09 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 12, 1909; UP056.001.005.00060; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.81 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 26, 1909; UP056.001.005.00061; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.81 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 3, 1909; UP056.001.005.00062; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.76 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 10, 1909; UP056.001.005.00063; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.70 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 17, 1909; UP056.001.005.00064; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.77 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 24, 1909; UP056.001.005.00065; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.24 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 1, 1909; UP056.001.005.00066; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.08 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 7, 1909; UP056.001.005.00067; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.13 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 19, 1909; UP056.001.005.00068; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.30 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 23, 1909; UP056.001.006.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.07 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 30, 1909; UP056.001.006.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.95 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 7, 1909; UP056.001.006.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.98 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [All Around Club] Reception to Freshman.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 14, 1909; UP056.001.006.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.92 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 21, 1909; UP056.001.006.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 28, 1909; UP056.001.006.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.95 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 4, 1909; UP056.001.006.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 11, 1909; UP056.001.006.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.71 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 18, 1909; UP056.001.006.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.18 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 2, 1909; UP056.001.006.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.90 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 9, 1909; UP056.001.006.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.91 Megabytes (Box 6)
    Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 16, 1909; UP056.001.006.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.65 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 23, 1909; UP056.001.006.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.41 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 13, 1910; UP056.001.006.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.52 Megabytes (Box 6)
    All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 20, 1910; UP056.001.006.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.83 Megabytes (Box 6)
    All Around Club. Alpha Kappa Delta. [American institute of electrical engineers] Meeting held at Tufts, January 8, 1910
  - Tufts Weekly, January 27, 1910; UP056.001.006.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.74 Megabytes (Box 6)
    All Around Club. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 10, 1910; UP056.001.006.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.10 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 17, 1910; UP056.001.006.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.12 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 24, 1910; UP056.001.006.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.64 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 3, 1910; UP056.001.006.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.54 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 10, 1910; UP056.001.006.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.36 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [Alumni association] Appeal for funds to establish a suitable memorial to Dean Shipman
  - Tufts Weekly, March 17, 1910; UP056.001.006.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.34 Megabytes (Box 6)
    All Around Club; Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, March 24, 1910; UP056.001.006.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.60 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 31, 1910; UP056.001.006.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.45 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [Aero Club] Meeting held to organize club, p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 7, 1910; UP056.001.006.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.81 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 21, 1910; UP056.001.006.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.61 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1910; UP056.001.006.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.77 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 5, 1910; UP056.001.006.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.41 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 12, 1910; UP056.001.006.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [Aero Club] Meeting held to organize club, p. 2. Alpha Kappa Delta; Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, May 19, 1910; UP056.001.006.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [Aero Club] meeting held to organize club, p. 4.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 26, 1910; UP056.001.006.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.64 Megabytes (Box 6)
    Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, June 2, 1910; UP056.001.006.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.26 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 9, 1910; UP056.001.006.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.68 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 16, 1910; UP056.001.006.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.64 Megabytes (Box 6)
    Alpha Kappa Delta. Alpha Omicron Pi; Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, September 29, 1910; UP056.001.006.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.68 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 4, 1910; UP056.001.006.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.20 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1910; UP056.001.006.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.37 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [Aero Club] meeting held to organize club, p. 2.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 18, 1910; UP056.001.006.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.29 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [Aero Club] meeting held to organize club, p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 25, 1910; UP056.001.006.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.56 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 1, 1910; UP056.001.006.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.36 Megabytes (Box 6)
    Academic Honors p. 1; [Aero Club] meeting held to organize club, p. 4.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 8, 1910; UP056.001.006.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.12 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 15, 1910; UP056.001.006.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.23 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 22, 1910; UP056.001.006.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.45 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 6, 1910; UP056.001.006.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.79 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 13, 1910; UP056.001.006.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.32 Megabytes (Box 6)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 20, 1910; UP056.001.006.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.43 Megabytes (Box 6)
    All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 10, 1911; UP056.001.006.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.98 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 17, 1911; UP056.001.006.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.59 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 24, 1911; UP056.001.006.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.39 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 31, 1911; UP056.001.006.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.74 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [All Around Club] Junior Play. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 8, 1911; UP056.001.006.00051; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.14 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 14, 1911; UP056.001.006.00052; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.60 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 21, 1911; UP056.001.006.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 28, 1911; UP056.001.006.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.98 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [Aero Club] includes photo, p. 1; Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, March 7, 1911; UP056.001.006.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.90 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 14, 1911; UP056.001.006.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.97 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [All Around Club] Sophmore Play.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 21, 1911; UP056.001.006.00057; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.97 Megabytes (Box 6)
    All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi; Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, March 28, 1911; UP056.001.006.00058; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.32 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 4, 1911; UP056.001.006.00059; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.97 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 11, 1911; UP056.001.006.00060; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.77 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [All Around Club] Operetta, "Jack and the Baked-Bean Stalk"; Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 25, 1911; UP056.001.006.00061; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.34 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [All Around Club] Operetta, "Jack and the Baked-Bean Stalk".
  - Tufts Weekly, May 2, 1911; UP056.001.006.00062; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.40 Megabytes (Box 6)
    [All Around Club] Operetta, "Jack and the Baked-Bean Stalk". Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 9, 1911; UP056.001.006.00063; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.67 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 16, 1911; UP056.001.006.00064; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.04 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 23, 1911; UP056.001.006.00065; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.64 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 30, 1911; UP056.001.006.00066; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.59 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 6, 1911; UP056.001.006.00067; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.24 Megabytes (Box 6)
    All Around Club. [Aero Club] includes photo, p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 13, 1911; UP056.001.006.00068; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.34 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 21, 1911; UP056.001.006.00069; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.74 Megabytes (Box 6)
    Alumni day; Alumni field day
  - Tufts News, 1912; UP056.001.063.00001 (Box Volume 63)
    Four issues published in 1912 by the Class of 1913 as a temporary substitute for The Tufts Weekly.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 12, 1913; UP056.001.007.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.51 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 19, 1913; UP056.001.007.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.08 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 26, 1913; UP056.001.007.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.69 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly,December 3, 1913; UP056.001.007.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.25 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly,December 10, 1913; UP056.001.007.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.82 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 17, 1913; UP056.001.007.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.81 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 7, 1914; UP056.001.007.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.27 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 14, 1914; UP056.001.007.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.59 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 21, 1914; UP056.001.007.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.09 Megabytes (Box 7)
    [All Around Club] Presents "In Gilbert and Sullivan Land" (incl. photos and programs).
  - Tufts Weekly, January 28, 1914; UP056.001.007.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.87 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 11, 1914; UP056.001.007.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.95 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 18, 1914; UP056.001.007.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.41 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 25 1914, UP056.001.007.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.71 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 4, 1914; UP056.001.007.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.57 Megabytes (Box 7)
    All Around Club; Various alumni organizations arrange for banquet and grand reunion, March 7, 1914, p1
  - Tufts Weekly, March 11, 1914; UP056.001.007.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 7)
    All Around Club; Various alumni organizations arrange for banquet and grand reunion, March 7, 1914, p1,6
  - Tufts Weekly, March 18, 1914; UP056.001.007.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.01 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 25, 1914; UP056.001.007.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.88 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Various alumni organizations arrange for banquet and grand reunion, March 7, 1914, p1,4
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1914; UP056.001.007.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.99 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 8, 1914; UP056.001.007.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.19 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 14, 1914; UP056.001.007.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.82 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 29, 1914; UP056.001.007.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.26 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1914; UP056.001.007.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.55 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 13, 1914; UP056.001.007.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.53 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. [Alumni and Faculty, Famous] Names of Tufts graduates included in "Woman's Who's Who of America", p.5. [Alumni and Faculty, Famous 1912-13] List of Tufts graduates in 1912-13 issue of "Who's Who in America". p.3.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 20, 1914; UP056.001.007.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.83 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 27, 1914; UP056.001.007.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.35 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 3, 1914; UP056.001.007.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.35 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Additional user copies in the Reading Room. Alumni day
  - Tufts Weekly, June 13, 1914; UP056.001.007.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.94 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 23, 1914; UP056.001.007.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.52 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the reading room.
  - Tufts Weekly, September 30, 1914; UP056.001.007.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.37 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 7, 1914; UP056.001.007.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.62 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 14, 1914; UP056.001.007.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.01 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 21, 1914; UP056.001.007.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.09 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 28, 1914; UP056.001.007.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.22 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 4, 1914; UP056.001.007.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.75 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 11, 1914; UP056.001.007.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.78 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 18, 1914; UP056.001.007.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.11 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 25, 1914; UP056.001.007.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.72 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 2, 1914; UP056.001.007.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.38 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 9, 1914; UP056.001.007.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.07 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 16, 1914; UP056.001.007.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.26 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 13, 1915; UP056.001.007.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.05 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 20, 1915; UP056.001.007.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.14 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 27, 1915; UP056.001.007.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.67 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 10, 1915; UP056.001.007.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.64 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 17, 1915; UP056.001.007.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.73 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 24, 1915; UP056.001.007.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.85 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 3, 1915; UP056.001.007.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.55 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 10, 1915; UP056.001.007.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.32 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. Tufts alumni who hav won fame in the educational world, p4
  - Tufts Weekly, March 17, 1915; UP056.001.007.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.58 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 24, 1915; UP056.001.007.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.42 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 31, 1915; UP056.001.007.00051; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.51 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 7, 1915; UP056.001.007.00052; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.41 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1915; UP056.001.007.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.53 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. [All Around Club] To present Charles Vincent's operetta, "The Japanese Girl", April 30 and May 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 5, 1915; UP056.001.007.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.78 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 12, 1915; UP056.001.007.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.15 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 19, 1915; UP056.001.007.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.26 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 26, 1915; UP056.001.007.00057; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.18 Megabytes (Box 7)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. [Admissions, 1915]. Entrance Requirements. All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 2, 1915; UP056.001.007.00058; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.61 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 12, 1915; UP056.001.007.00059; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.69 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 29, 1915; UP056.001.008.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.25 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. AMRAD [American Radio and Research Corporation] Wireless tower blown over in gale, pp 1, 4; All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 6, 1915; UP056.001.008.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.80 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. AMRAD [American Radio and Research Corporation] Wireless tower blown over in gale, p 1
  - Tufts Weekly, October 13, 1915; UP056.001.008.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.60 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. Jackson Alumnae notes; AMRAD [American Radio and Research Corporation] Wireless tower blown over in gale, p 1
  - Tufts Weekly, October 20, 1915; UP056.001.008.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.83 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. Jackson alumnae notes; AMRAD [American Radio and Research Corporation] Wireless tower blown over in gale, p 4
  - Tufts Weekly, October 27, 1915; UP056.001.008.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.52 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 3, 1915; UP056.001.008.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.09 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 10, 1915; UP056.001.008.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.63 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 17, 1915; UP056.001.008.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.71 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. Academic Honors, 1913- 1920 p.1
  - Tufts Weekly, November 24, 1915; UP056.001.008.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.58 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 1, 1915; UP056.001.008.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.50 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 8, 1915; UP056.001.008.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.69 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 15, 1915; UP056.001.008.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.72 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 5, 1916; UP056.001.008.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.75 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 12, 1916; UP056.001.008.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.70 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 19, 1916; UP056.001.008.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.61 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 26, 1916; UP056.001.008.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.67 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 2, 1916; UP056.001.008.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.66 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 16, 1916; UP056.001.008.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.27 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 23, 1916; UP056.001.008.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.65 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. John Coleman Adams (1870). When Tufts and I Were Young (poem). Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 1, 1916; UP056.001.008.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.35 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 8, 1916; UP056.001.008.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.82 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 15, 1916; UP056.001.008.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.55 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 22, 1916; UP056.001.008.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.23 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 29, 1916; UP056.001.008.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.14 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 5, 1916; UP056.001.008.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.60 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 12, 1916; UP056.001.008.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.77 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 26, 1916; UP056.001.008.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.73 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1916; UP056.001.008.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.56 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 10, 1916; UP056.001.008.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.98 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 17, 1916; UP056.001.008.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.26 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 24, 1916; UP056.001.008.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.26 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 31, 1916; UP056.001.008.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.17 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 7, 1916; UP056.001.008.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.38 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. All Around Club;[Alumni] Outing at Canobie Lake in place of Field Day, 1
  - Tufts Weekly, June 21, 1916; UP056.001.008.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.95 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the reading room. All Around Club; Woman's Who's Who in America, includes many Tufts graduates; [Alumni] Outing at Canobie Lake in place of field day, pp1,5
  - Tufts Weekly, September 27, 1916; UP056.001.008.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.79 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 4, 1916; UP056.001.008.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.54 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1916; UP056.001.008.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.73 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copies in the Reading Room.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 18, 1916; UP056.001.008.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.85 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 25, 1916; UP056.001.008.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.78 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 1, 1916; UP056.001.008.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.88 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 8, 1916; UP056.001.008.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.47 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 15, 1916; UP056.001.008.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.22 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors, 1913- 1920 p.1
  - Tufts Weekly, November 22, 1916; UP056.001.008.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.33 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 29, 1916; UP056.001.008.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.08 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 6, 1916; UP056.001.008.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.04 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 13, 1916; UP056.001.008.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.58 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 20, 1916; UP056.001.008.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.96 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 1, 1917; UP056.001.008.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.71 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 10, 1917; UP056.001.008.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.65 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 17, 1917; UP056.001.008.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.96 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alumni issue
  - Tufts Weekly, January 24, 1917; UP056.001.008.00051; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.21 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 31, 1917; UP056.001.008.00052; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.46 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 14, 1917; UP056.001.008.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.01 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 21, 1917; UP056.001.008.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.21 Megabytes (Box 8)